http://www.raganandmassey.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
We respect your right to privacy. This statement explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information.
What is Personal Information?
Personal information is any information that we can use to identify you as an individual. This may include: Name, Address, Email Address or Phone Number.
We do not collect age information and do not knowingly collect information from individuals under the age of 18.
Collection of Personal Information
We only collect personal information that you provide when you fill out our Contact Form.
This may vary when special promotions are offered.
Sharing of Personal Information
Your personal information is used only to respond directly to your inquiry. It is not shared with any third party, unless this is necessary to respond to your inquiry.
Special promotions may require that we share personal information with a third party in order to fulfill the promise of a special promotion.
Protection of Personal Information
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How to Contact Us
Please refer to the Contact page for contact information.
Changes to this Statement
We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. When changes are made, the date at the top of the page will also be changed.
